

KAZEEM SODIK ISOLA

ELECTRONICS AND ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

kazeemsodikisola@gmail.com

- 08149294051
- O No 1, Rev. Jacob Adenubi Close, Yekini Balogun Town Majek, Ajah Lagos
- in State. https://www.linkedin.com/in/sodik-kazeem-4b6333131

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am an Electrical and Electronics Engineering Graduate with 5+ years of experience working with companies in the Electrical industry and Education Industry. Implementation of digital systems was a primary focus. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, and possess a wide range of technical skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship (SIWES)

June 2015 - August 2015

HWI Consult, Mokola Ibadan, Oyo State.

Monitoring and Supervision of Electrical and Electronics installations.

Activities

- · Design of Electrical Plan
- Monitoring and supervising site installation.
- Give correctional details of Electrical and Electronics installation fault observations

Internship Industrial Attachment

August 2016 - March 2017

Scrotonic Nigeria Limited, Warri

Delta State.

Installation, Service and Maintenance of

Sharp Photocopiers. Activities

- Changing of consumables e.g. Toner, Developer, Toner IC, and Fusing Unit broken parts.
- · Maintenance of Optical Unit and LSU

Junior Engineer June 2018–Dec2021

Scrotonic Nigeria Limited, Warri

Delta State.

Installation, Service and Maintenance of Sharp

Photocopiers. Activities

- Changing of consumables e.g. Toner, Developer, Toner IC, and Fusing Unit broken parts.
- Maintenance of Optical Unit and LSU

April 2022- Present

Online Moderator

SuperProf, GauthExpert, One Class and Preply

Online Physics, Mathematics and Chemistry Instructor.

Activities

- Provide High Quality Solutions for students
- Moderate Instructors Solutions
- Help students get more insight on the topic and not only solution to the problem provided

EDUCATION

BSc. Electronics and Electrical Engineering

January 2011 - June 2017

Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile Ife Osun State.

SKILLS

- ❖ Microsoft Packages e.g. Microsoft Word, Excel, Power Point etc.
- * MATLAB, Simulink and LabView, and National Instrument (NI).
- ❖ GeoGebra, Desmos, Photomath, Geometry Pad, Math Editor etc.
- ❖ Programming Languages Like C, Python, HTML, CSS, Java script etc.

REFEREES

Engr. Ajayi Adeshina (Scrotronic Nig. Ltd.) General Manager of Scrotronic Nig Ltd. 08039679359 Relationship (Uncle) Mr. Adenubi Peter
Proprietor of God Canopy School
08067242872
Relationship (Employer)